The day to make your mark...Don't skip it.
Senior Skip Day is a comedy film directed by Nick Weiss.
The senior class plans to have a skip-day party at the principal's house until Adam Harris leaks
the secret, so he decides to save the celebration by hosting it at his house.
Adam Harris, played by Gary Lundy.
Mr. Frankfurt Dickwalder, played by Larry Miller.
Cathleen Harris, played by Lea Thompson.
Ellen Harris, played by Tara Reid.
Cara, played by Kayla Ewell.
Scott, played by Talan Torriero.
Skip Day or Senior Skip Day is a long-standing tradition in most American and Canadian high schools and junior
high school where the senior class will excuse themselves from school on a pre-determined day.
Skip Day or Senior Skip Day may also refer to:
"Skip Day" (The Cleveland Show), a season 3
episode
"Senior Skip Day", a song by American rapper Mac Miller from the 2010 album K.I.D.S.
"Skip Day", a 2014 episode of Odd Squad
Skip Day, a 2018 documentary short film by Ivete Lucas
Senior Skip
Day, a 2008 direct-to-DVD film starring Larry Miller, Lea Thompson, Tara Reid, and Kayla Ewell
The film explores themes of high school, house party,
principal, school principal, debauchery.
The tone is lighthearted.